A Bewitching New Live-Action Movie!
Casper Meets Wendy is a family, fantasy, comedy film directed by Sean McNamara.
When a warlock threatens Wendy the Good Little Witch, she and her aunts hide out
at a resort where Casper the Ghost is vacationing with his uncles.
Although Casper and Wendy are told ghosts and witches
don't get along, the two are kindred spirits!
This spooky family-friendly adventure finds Casper and Wendy bridging the
ghost-witch divide to battle the warlock who is intent on destroying Wendy.
Wendy, played by Hilary Duff.
Gabby, played by Shelley Duvall.
Geri, played by Cathy Moriarty.
Fanny, played by Teri Garr.
Desmond Spellman, played by George Hamilton.
Casper (voice), played by Jeremy Foley.
Casper Meets Wendy is a 1998 American fantasy comedy film based on the Harvey Comics
cartoon characters Casper the Friendly Ghost and Wendy the Good Little Witch.
The film is a standalone sequel to Casper: A Spirited Beginning,
and the second spin-off/prequel of Casper (1995).
Saban Entertainment co-produced the project.
This was Hilary Duff's first major film, and was released on
September 22, 1998, six days before her 11th birthday.
The film also marks the second Casper film for co-star Cathy Moriarty, who
previously starred as the main antagonist in the 1995 film.
The film was met with mostly negative reviews from critics, but
was considered an improvement to its predecessor.
Its television premiere was October 24, 1999 on Fox Family.
The tone is lighthearted.